Guide to the Lingnan Foundation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
Lingnan Foundation records
1951-2010
1980-2006
RG 14A
Yale University Divinity School Library
16
(38 boxes)
This collection is the official archives of the Lingnan Foundation, formerly known as the Trustees of Lingnan University, which is a grant-making independent organization that seeks to contribute to the advancement of higher education in South China. These records are a continuation of documentation found in Yale Divinity School Record Group No. 14, Archives of the Trustees of Lingnan University.
Lingnan Foundation
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Lingnan Foundation, 2012
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The Lingnan Foundation, formerly the Trustees of Lingnan University, was first incorporated in the State of New York in 1893 to support the development of a college in Canton (Guangzhou), China, which had begun to offer classes in 1888. This college later became Lingnan University.
After the change of government in China in 1949, the Arts and Sciences faculties of Lingnan University were merged with Sun Yat-sen (Zhongshan) University. From 1954 to 1979, the Trustees conducted their work primarily in Hong Kong with several colleges that became the Chinese University of Hong Kong, and later, with the institution that is now Lingnan University, Hong Kong.
In 1980, the Trustees resumed their activities in Guangzhou, principally with Sun Yat-sen (Zhongshan) University on the former Lingnan campus and, since 1988, with Sun Yat-sen (Zhongshan's) constituent, Lingnan (University) College.
The Lingnan Foundation considers Lingnan University, Hong Kong and Sun Yat-sen University, including Lingnan (University) College as partner institutions. The Foundation also supports institutions or organizations in the United States or elsewhere that reflect the Lingnan tradition or otherwise share the Foundation's objectives in developing and strengthening its partner institutions.
Scope and Contents
These archives are a continuation of documentation found in Record Group No. 14, Archives of the Trustees of Lingnan University. There is some overlap between the two collections. The bulk of the material in this record group dates from 1980 to 2006. Series I, Board of Trustees Meetings, includes agendas, reports, minutes, and correspondence related to the bi-annual meetings of the Board. Series II, Board of Trustees Records, documents other activities of the Board, including trips to China and Hong Kong to visit partner organizations and administrative arrangements for the Trustees of Lingnan University/Lingnan Foundation. The Committee Records in Series III and Financial Records of Series V primarily document the financial and adminstrative aspects of the Lingnan Foundation while the Program Records in Series IV document the many programs that the Foundation has supported over the years. Correspondence of longtime Executive Director/President Douglas Murray, as well as of other organizational leaders, is found throughout the collection.
Arrangement
I. Board of Trustees Meetings
II. Board of Trustees Records
III. Committee Records
IV. Program Records
V. Financial Records
Education -- China; Universities and colleges -- China -- Religion; Ling nan da xue (Guangzhou, China)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1980-2006; Series I
  - May meeting preliminary correspondence, report of C.K. Yang trip to China, 1980 Jan -Mar (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - May meeting grant requests, Ad Hoc Planning Committee recommendations, 1980 Mar - Apr (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - May meeting agenda, minutes, reports, 1980 May-Jun (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - November meeting correspondence, reports, 1980 Jul - Oct (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - November meeting agenda, reports, minutes, 1980 Nov (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - November meeting reports, notes, 1980 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - May meeting agenda, reports, minutes, 1981 Jan-May (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - May meeting reports, letter from Zhongshan (Sun Yatsen) University, 1981 Apr- May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, minutes, 1981 May - Nov (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - November meeting reports, correspondence, 1981 Jul - Oct (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 1981 Nov - 1982 May (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, minutes, 1982 May - Nov (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - November meeting reports, proposals, 1982 Sep - Nov (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, minutes, 1982 Nov - 1983 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - May meeting reports, proposals, 1983 Jan - May (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1983 Nov (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - November meeting reports, proposals, minutes, 1983 Nov (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1983 Dec - 1984 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - May meeting reports, proposals, minutes, 1984 May (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Douglas Murray, Executive Director, correspondence, reports, clippings sent to Trustees, 1984 Jul - Oct (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1984 Jun - Nov (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - November meeting reports, proposals, minutes, 1984 Nov (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - November meeting reports, proposals; correspondence of Douglas Murray, 1984 Nov (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - May meeting announcement, Douglas Murray correspondence, 1985 Jan-May (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - May meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 1985 May (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - May meeting reports, proposals, 1985 May (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, minutes; correspondence of Douglas Murray, 1985 Sep - Nov (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - November meeting reports, 1985 Nov (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - November meeting reports, photos, 1985 Nov (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - April meeting announcement, agenda, reports, minutes, 1986 Feb - Apr (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - April meeting reports, 1986 Mar - Apr (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, minutes, correspondence, 1986 Aug - Nov (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - November meeting reports, correspondence, 1986 Nov - Dec (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, correspondence, 1986 Dec - 1987 May (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1987 May (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - December meeting announcement, agenda, articles mailed to Trustees, 1987 Aug- Dec (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - December meeting reports, correspondence, 1987 Oct - Dec (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - December meeting reports, 1987 Dec (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - December meeting reports, minutes (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - May meeting correspondence, agenda, mailings to Trustees, 1988 Apr - May (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - May meeting reports, 1988 May (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1988 May (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, mailings to Trustees, 1988 Oct - Nov (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - November meeting financial, legal reports, 1988 Nov (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - November meeting program reports, 1988 Nov (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - November meeting minutes, photo, 1988 Nov (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - June meeting announcement, agenda, mailings, 1989 Mar - Jun (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - June meeting reports, 1989 Jun (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - June meeting program reports, 1989 Jun (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - June meeting program reports, 1989 Jun (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - June meeting minutes, 1989 Jun (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - December meeting announcement, agenda, mailings, 1989 Sep - Dec (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - December meeting reports, 1989 Dec (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - December meeting reports, 1989 Dec (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - December meeting minutes, 1989 Dec (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, correspondence of Douglas Murray and James Bowers re. Zhongshan., 1990 Apr - May (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1990 May (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1990 Sep - Nov (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - November meeting reports, 1990 Nov (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1990 Nov (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - May meeting agenda, mailings, reports, 1991 May (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1991 May (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - November meeting agenda, reports, correspondence, 1991 Nov (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1991 Nov (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - May meeting correspondence, mailings, agenda, 1991 Dec - 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - May meeting reports, 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - November meeting announcement, correspondence, reports, 1992 Aug - Nov (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1992 Nov (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - November meeting reports, 1992 Nov (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - May meeting correspondence, reports, 1993 Feb - May (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - May meeting reports, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - May meeting reports, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - May meeting reports, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - November meeting correspondence, mailings, 1993 Oct - Nov (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - November meeting reports, 1993 Nov (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - November meeting reports, 1993 Nov (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - November meeting reports, 1993 Nov (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1993 Nov (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - May meeting correspondence, reports, 1994 Mar - May (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - May meeting reports, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - May meeting reports, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - November meeting agenda, correspondence, reports, 1994 Oct - Nov (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - November meeting reports, 1994 Nov (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - November meeting reports, 1994 Nov (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1994 Nov (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1995 Mar - May (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - May meeting reports, 1995 May (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1995 May (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, mailings, reports, 1995 Nov (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - November meeting reports, 1995 Nov (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1995 Nov (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - May meeting agenda, correspondence, reports, 1996 Apr - May (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1996 May (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1996 Sep - Nov (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1996 Nov (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - May meeting agenda, mailings, reports, 1997 May (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1997 May (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Yale-China Association, November meeting agenda, reports, 1997 Oct - Nov (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1997 Nov (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1998 Mar - May (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - May meeting reports, 1998 May (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - May meeting reports; special session on Future Program Directions, minutes, 1998 May (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, paper on "Major Strategic Issues for Chinese Higher Education in the 21st Century", November meeting agenda, reports, 1998 Jul - Nov (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1998 Nov (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - May meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 1999 Mar - May (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - May meeting reports, minutes, 1999 May (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, mailings, reports, 1999 Jul - Nov (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 1999 Nov (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Memos re. Special Board Meeting, January 31, 2000 Jan (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - April meeting announcement, agenda, mailings, reports, 2000 Feb - Apr (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - April meeting reports, 2000 Apr (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - November meeting agenda, "Thoughts About the Board", reports, 2000 Aug - Nov (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - November meeting reports, 2000 Nov (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 2000 Nov (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - April meeting announcement, mailings, agenda, reports, 2001 Mar - Apr (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - April meeting reports, 2001 Apr (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - November meeting announcement, agenda, reports, 2001 Oct - Nov (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - November meeting reports, minutes, 2001 Nov (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - May meeting correspondence, agenda, reports, 2002 May (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - May meeting reports, proposals, 2002 May (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - November meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2002 Nov (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - April meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2003 Apr (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - November meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2003 Nov (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - May meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2004 May (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - November meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2004 Nov (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - May meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2005 May (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - November meeting agenda, reports, proposals, minutes, 2005 Nov (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - May meeting agenda, reports, proposals, 2006 May (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Board of Trustees Records, 1979-2005; Series II
  - Trips taken by Trustees and staff
    - Douglas Murray trip to Zhongshan (Sun Yatsen) University, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Murray to Hong Kong, 1985 Jul (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou (Zhongshan University), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, including photos, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Nancy Chapman to Guangzhou, 1988 Jan (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1988 Mar (Box 10)
    - Chapman to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1989 Jan - Feb (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Chapman, Murray, Russell Phillips to Guangzhou, 1989 Aug (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Murray to Guangzhou, HK, 1990 Jan (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1990 Jun (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1990 Jun (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1990 Jun (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Murray to Guangzhou, 1991 Jul (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1993 Jun (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1993 May (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Phillips, Murray to Hong Kong, 1994 Jan (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Jerome Grieder to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1994 Jun (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, including photos, 1994 Nov (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Murray, Chapman,Terrill Lautz, Karl Lo to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1995 Jun (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Leslie Stone to Hong Kong, China, 1995 Aug-Sep (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Murray to Hong Kong, China, 1996 Mar (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Austin Frank to Hong Kong, China, 1996 Jun (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Murray to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1997 Jan (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1997 Jun (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 1997 Jun (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, including photos, 1998 Jun (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Nanjing, 1999 Jun (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Nanjing, including photos, 1999 Jun (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Murray to Hong Kong, 1999 Sep (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, including photos, 2000 Jun (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 2001 Jan (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 2001 Jun (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Delegation to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 2002 Mar (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Delegations to Hong Kong, Guangzhou, 2003 - 2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Individual files
    - Yorke Allen (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tristan Beplat (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Mark Buchman (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Mary Brown Bullock (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Chan Wing-Tsit (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Nancy Chapman (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Robert Chin (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Ralph Clough (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Jonathan Colby (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Frances Connick (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Peter Cooke (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Charles T. Cross (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - John D. Eusden (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - James Feinerman (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - C. Coleman Fisher (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Henry S. Frank (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Carl J. Green (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Richard M. Henry (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Terrill E. Lautz (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Sui-Ming Lee (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Joy C. Light (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Y. M. Lin (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - William F. McCalpin (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Christian Murck (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Russell A. Phillips, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Seton Shanley (Box 13, Folder 10a)
    - Helen F. S. Siu (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - William Speidel (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Stephen H. Stackpole (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Gene C. Szutu (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Susan Wallace (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - C. K. Yang (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Alice Young (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Mailings and correspondence
    - Trustee mailings, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Trustee mailings, 1992-1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Trustee mailings, 2001-2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Administrative arrangements, 1995-2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Regarding pensions, pensioners, 1979-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Committee Records, 1951-2005; Series III
  - Ad Hoc Planning Committee, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Audit Committee, 1971-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Audit Committee, 1994-2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Finance Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Finance Committee, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Finance Committee, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Finance Committee, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee, 1997-1999, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1974, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee, 1951-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Nominating Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Nominating Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Nominating Committee, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Nominating Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Nominating Committee, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Nominating Committee, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Nominating Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Nominating Committee, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Nominating Committee, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Search Committee for President, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Program Records, 1979-2010; Series IV
  - Lingnan College /Lingnan (University) College at Zhongshan University
    - Chronological files, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 2005-2008 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Trustees of L(U)C correspondence, documents, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - MBA program / China Executive MBA (CHEMBA), 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Brochure (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Lingnan College/University, Hong Kong
    - Chronological files, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 1999-2000, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Study Tour, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Cross Straights Library Conference, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Centre for Asian Pacific Studies, 1985-1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Centre for Asian Pacific Studies, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Centre for Asian Pacific Studies, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Centre for Asian Pacific Studies, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Centre for Asian Pacific Studies - Graduate Internship, 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Centre for Modern Literature in Chinese, 1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Chen Building Grant, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Joint Project on Aging with Zhongshan University, 1989-1995 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Practicum in PRC for management students, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Translation program, 1989-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Zhongshan University (Sun Yat-sen University)
    - Library / DLIS
      - Correspondence and reports regarding grants and programs for Library and Department of Library and Information Science, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Zhongshan University Library System Development Plan: project with University of California, San Diego, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and reports, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and reports, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence and reports, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Journals Subscription grants, 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)